Good afternoon.
下午好.
I believe that this house is for sale.
我想这房子是要出售的吧!
That's right.
是的.
May I have a look at it, please?
我可以看一看吗?
Yes, of course. Come in.
可以,当然可以.请进.
How long have you lived here?
您在这里住了多长时间?
I've live here for twenty years.
我在这里已经住了20年了.
Twenty years!
20年!
That's a long time.
这个时间可不短.
Yes, I've been here since 1976.
是啊,从1976年起我就住在这里.
Then why do you want to sell it?
那么,您为什么要卖掉它呢?
Because I've just retired.
因为我刚退休.
I want to buy a small house in the country.
我想在乡下买幢小房子.
How much does this house cost?
这座房子卖多少钱?
£68, 500.
68,500英镑.
That's a lot of money.
那可真是一大笔钱呢!
It's worth every penny of it.
它确确实实值这么多钱.
Well, I like the house,
啊,我喜欢这房子,
but I can't decide yet.
但我还不能决定.
My wife must see it first.
我妻子必须先来看一看.
Women always have the last word.
女人总是最后说了算的.